</salt>

School of applied technology



Tamlyn Springer

I'm a South African - German living in Stockholm with a passion for coding & sustainable solutions. My enthusiasm for learning, solving complex issues, and making products that serve a purpose brought me to Salt. I have worked for some years in the retail industry, and have an educational background in biology and ecology.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

General

JavaScript Typescript

Frontend

React
Redux
Webpack
HTML
CSS/SASS/styled-components
TailwindCSS & Bootstrap

Backend

NodeJS ExpressJS REST GraphQL MongoDB/PostgreSQL

Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code
Mocha, Jest, Cypress
Docker
Git & GitHub
AWS
Cloud Platforms (MongoDB
Atlas, ElephantSQL,
Contentful)
CI/CD (Netlify, NextJS,
Railway)
TDD, agile work methods
Figma, Inkscape, Canva

Links

LinkedIn GitHub

Languages

English - Native German - Basic Swedish - Basic

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Full Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

September 2022 - December 2022 Intensive three-month training program for full-stack software development. With a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

Masters of Science - University of the Witwatersrand January 2017 - July 2019 Masters by research dissertation focusing on plant ecology and evolution.

Bachelor of Science with Honours - University of the Witwatersrand

February 2013 - December 2016

WORK EXPERIENCE

<u>Software developer portfolio</u> </salt> Post-graduate Program January 2023 - ongoing

Furthering my Typescript front-end and back-end skills.

Research analyst - Impaakt - remote

January 2021 - June 2022

Using published information to research and report how businesses impact the planet and society.

Store supervisor - Intende Action Wear - Johannesburg August 2020 - October 2021

Responsible for the sales, team training & operations of the store. Conducted sales analyses and inventory counts to assess targets and purchasing trends.

Store assistant - Intende Action Wear

November 2019 - July 2020

Teaching assistant - University of the Witwatersrand - Johannesburg

January 2016 - July 2019 Teaching assistant to BSc biology undergraduate students, courses included biostatistics and R programming.